runforyourlives.com 2013-10-28

# Privacy Policy | Run For Your Lives

## PRIVACY POLICY – COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

This site is owned and operated by Reed Street Productions. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

## INFORMATION REED STREET PRODUCTIONS GATHERS AND TRACKS

**Reed Street Productions gathers two types of information about users:**

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters and to share/email a friend.
  * Information Reed Street Productions gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Reed Street Productions sell any information about an individual user to a third party.

**Reed Street Productions Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:**

 **Optional Voluntary Information**  
We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

 **1\. Electronic newsletters policy**  
We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Reed Street Productions gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

 **2\. Tell A Friend Policy**  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking on share buttons located throughout the site. To share as an email, the user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

 **Children**  
Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

 **Usage tracking**  
Reed Street Productions tracks user traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Reed Street Productions does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

Reed Street Productions uses tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

 **Cookies**  
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Reed Street Productions uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above).

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling, and surveys.

 **Privacy Policy Use**  
How the information you gather is used if relevant.

## USE OF INFORMATION

Reed Street Productions uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our website, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. Reed Street Productions never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors, or partners.

## OPT-OUT POLICY

Reed Street Productions gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.

## YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Reed Street Productions. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. While we do not intend to make changes to this policy very often, it is always a good idea to double check our most current policy statement when you visit us to be sure that you have read and agree with what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Kimbia, Inc.Transaction Security Information can be viewed [here](http://www.kimbia.com/kimbiaEE/archive/2009/01/KIMBIA_Transaction_Security_2010.pdf).
